apponic.com 2017-07-16

# Privacy Policy

Trust is a cornerstone of our mission at Apponic. We are serious to regard the privacy of our users and committed to gaining and maintaining your trust.

### Information Collected

Apponic collects information concerning users in the following cases:

__Information you provide directly to Apponic Web Sites.__

  * When contact Apponic with necessary contact infomation required by Apponic website.
  * When register at Apponic as community user with necessary personal infomation required by Apponic website.

__Information we collect from AppTracker.__

  * The AppTracker will not collect any personal information.
  * The information collected is a list of programs and their versions, along with the operating system details to help with processing.

### Use of Information

Apponic use the information collected for the following purposes:

  * To send replies to user's contact for suggestions ,comments or proposals.
  * To create a community of users, where they can share their opinions, comments and favorites with other users.
  * To provide users' opinions about software through community or any other electronic means.
  * To inform community users about anything related to the software that they are interested in.
  * To improve your experience on Apponic.

Any information provided will NOT be sold or given to any third party(ies) by any means, and will only be used for sending the related information regarding user's privacy setting via email.

### User Privacy Control

Users will be allowed to choose and modify their privacy level regarding the personal data provided to Apponic through their personal menu.

  * Profile: 

Public Profile: All personal information related to the User is public. However, the option "Privacy settings" on the "My account" can be used to enable other users to see information related to "Visible to all users", "Activity page visible to all users" and "Favorites page visible to all users". User's avatar that represents them always be visible for all Users.

Private Profile: All personal information related to the User is private. Information related to "Visible to all users", "Activity page visible to all users" and "Favorites page visible to all users" will not be visible to the other users. User's avatar that represents them always be visible for all Users.

  * Subscriptions: 

The option "My subscriptions" can be used to enable Apponic to send newsletters to you related to "All About Software (weekly)", "Special software offers (occasional)".You can stop the delivery of commercial email messages from Apponic at any time.

### Cookies and IPs

The user agrees to cookies and IP tracking. Our software and the site's traffic analyzer use cookies and IP trackers that collect data for statistical purposes, including: number of visits, URL and domain, operating system, and browser. The User is also free to de-activate and/or eliminate cookies by following the instructions given by their Internet browser.

We use third-party advertising on this site includeing Google AdSense.The advertising system may use cookies to display advertising that relates to the pages viewed by the visitors.A cookie that allows Google to collect the information (not including your name, address , email address or telephone number) about the user's activity is activated in order to manage and publish advertisements.

The user is free to deactivate cookies in their browser.

### Questions regarding this Policy

If you have questions regarding the Apponic Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://www.apponic.com/info/contact/ "Contact us").
